{
    "question": "Contoh percakapan making and handling cancellation gimana ya?\r\nada yang bisa bantu",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "David : Excuse me. I think there is a mistake in our bill. We didn&#039;t have dinner here lst night.<br>Receptionist : I&#039;m sorry, sir. Here&#039;s the bill from the hotel restaurant. It&#039;s got your signature on it.<br>David : But that&#039;s not my signature. I&#039;d like to speak to the manager.<br>Receptionist : I&#039;m sorry, sir. The manager is busy.<br>Manager : You have a complaint about your bill, sir ?<br>David : Yes. I&#039;m afraid there&#039;s a mistake. We didn&#039;t have dinner in the restaurant last night.<br>Manager : But this looks like your signature on the restaurant bill.<br>Let me see. Oh dear I&#039;m very sorry. There&#039;s another couple called Morris in the hotel.<br>They had dinner last night. Not you. I do apologize.<br><br>sudah ya cukup :)\u00a0",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "tolong-describe-dengan-tema-my-beloved-home-407",
            "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "rumahku yg indah. bercat merah muda,di depannya dibuat pagar, di dalam terdiri dari ruang tamu,ruang keluarga,2 kamar mandi,2 tempat tidur. di belakang ada taman dipenuhi bunga bunga yg sangat indah dan ayunan <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "my home.. my everything.. even\u00a0my home not as huge the president home or a museums.. even my home don&#039;t as rich as the businessman home.. i love my home.. because my home protect me from the light of the sun , from the extreme weather , from the cold of the rain.. but i still love my home..home sweet home.. you&#039;re my protecter from childhood.. how bad you&#039;re you still my home... i called it my beloved home",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "whats-is-the-problem-from-the-story-snow-bride-858",
            "question": "Whats is the problem from the story \"Snow Bride\"",
            "attachments": [
                "question-attachments/whats-is-the-problem-from-the-story-snow-bride-858-1.docx"
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Carilah kata-kata yang terdengar janggal dan aneh... :)Mandiri lebih baik.<br>Okay ? @Liwed",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "lanjutan-jawaban-dari-in-the-developed-world-where-more-than-70-898",
            "question": "Lanjutan jawaban dari \"in the developed world, where more than 70% of citizens already live in cities, urbanization is spread evenly, and population growth\" pilihan nya    a. has slowed\r\nb. would slow\r\nc. slowed\r\nd. had slowed\r\ne. will slow\r\n(simple future tense)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "d. in the developed world, where more than 70% of citizens al already live in cities. urbanization is spread evenly. and population growth <u>had slowed</u>. <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "bisa saja isinya yang\u00a0<br>b. would slow, karena future pasti akan menggunakan will dan would adalah bentuk kedua dari modals tsb",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-beri-penjelasan-tentang-word-order-dengan-rinci-844",
            "question": "Tolong Beri Penjelasan Tentang Word Order\u00a0Dengan Rinci",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Word order atau tata urut kata merupakan cara untuk\nmenyusun kata \u2013 kata dalam urutan atau susunan yang tepat dan benar. </span>\n\n<br><br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Word order adalah susunan kata-kata dalam kalimat, artinya bahwa cara kita menempatkan setiap kata itu haruslah sesuai dengan fungsinya dalam membentuk suatu kalimat. Caranya dengan mengetahui dan menghafal rumus atau pola baku.<br>Contoh:<br>&#039;&#039; Sebuah mobil mewah baru buatan Amerika Serikat &#039;&#039; diterjemahkan menjadi \" A new American car \".<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "boleh-minta-contoh-soal-dari-ungkapan-maksud-532",
            "question": "Boleh minta contoh soal dari ungkapan maksud?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Maksud -&gt; Idea or opinion<br><br>I think the best way to be expert in mathematics is by practicing everyday.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-certia-bahasa-inggris-last-vocation-892",
            "question": "Contoh certia bahasa inggris \"last vocation\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "It&#039;s curious as we grow older, how easy it is to lose our sense of \ndirection, a sense of vocation, a sense of God&#039;s calling us to important\n things still to be done. Vocations are not just for the young starting \nout in marriage, a career, or religious life. There&#039;s another kind of \nvocation \u2014 a kind of \"late vocation\" \u2014 God&#039;s final call to a strong \nfinish. It is God&#039;s call to each one of us to grow old gracefully \u2014 full\n of grace \u2014 to grow toward Him.    \nGod calls us to respond heroically, like Saint Paul, pouring ourselves \nout like a libation until we can say: \"I have fought the good fight, I \nhave finished the race, I have kept the faith\" (II Tm 7).<span><br><br><br>INI</span>\u00a0?\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-simple-present-tense-verbal-dan-nominal-787",
            "question": "Contoh simple present tense, verbal dan nominal",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Simple Present Tense : Subject + V1 + keterangan waktu yang biasa dilakukan.ex : usually, every, always, often, sometimes,once, a week, a twice, etc.<br>Contohnya : he runs very quickly",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "pengertian-dan-contoh-adverb-of-frequency-256",
            "question": "Pengertian dan contoh adverb of frequency",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "adverb yang menggambarkan frekuensi seseorang melakukan suatu pekerjaan, misalnya setiap hari, atau beberapa kali dalam 1 bulan<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "pengertian\u00a0: kata keterangan yang menyatakan seberapa sering suatu kegiatan yang dilakukan.",
                    "attachments": [
                        "answer-attachments/pengertian-dan-contoh-adverb-of-frequency-256-1.gif"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kalimat-bahasa-inggris-noun-clause-387",
            "question": "Kalimat bahasa inggris\u00a0noun clause",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "I forgot that the fact was very important<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "mungkin yang first conditional,second conditional,sama third conditional<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "their-motivationimprove-if-they-858",
            "question": "Their motivation...............(improve) if they..........................(kick) a goal during the first half",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "their motivation increases when the kick goal during the first half<br><br>kalau salah gak apa-apa ya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}